const CounterData = [{
        question: "Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for applications with varying compute workloads?",
        a: "A) Amazon EC2 costs are billed on a monthly basis",
        b: "B) Users retain full administrative access to their Amazon EC2 instances",
        c: "C) Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on demand when needed",
        d: "D) Users can permanently run enough instances to handle peak workloads",
        correct: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "Which AWS service would simplify the migration of a database to AWS?",
        a: "A) AWS Storage Gateway",
        b: "B) AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
        c: "C) Amazon EC2",
        d: "D) Amazon AppStream 2.0",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Which AWS offering enables users to find, buy, and immediately start using software solutions in their AWS environment ?",
        a: "A) AWS Config",
        b: "B) AWS OpsWorks",
        c: "C) AWS SDK",
        d: "D) AWS Marketplace",
        correct: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "Which AWS networking service enables a company to create a virtual network within AWS?",
        a: "A) AWS Config",
        b: "B) Amazon Route 53",
        c: "C) AWS Direct Connect",
        d: "D) Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)",
        correct: "d",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is an AWS responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
        a: "A) Configuring third-party applications",
        b: "B) Maintaining physical hardware ",
        c: "C) Securing application access and data",
        d: "D) Managing guest operating systems",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Which component of the AWS global infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront use to ensure low-latency delivery?",
        a: "A) AWS Regions",
        b: "B) Edge locations",
        c: "C) Availability Zones",
        d: "D) Virtual Private Cloud (VPC)",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "How would a system administrator add an additional layer of login security to a user's AWS Management Console?",
        a: "A) Use Amazon Cloud Directory",
        b: "B) Audit AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles",
        c: "C) Enable multi-factor authentication",
        d: "D) Enable AWS CloudTrail",
        correct: "c",
    },
    {
        question: "Which service can identify the user that made the API call when an Amazon EC2 instance is terminated?",
        a: "A) AWS Trusted Advisor",
        b: "B) AWS CloudTrail",
        c: "C) AWS X-Ray",
        d: "D) AWS Identity and Access Management (AWS IAM)",
        correct: "b",
    },
    {
        question: "Which service would be used to send alerts based on Amazon CloudWatch alarms?",
        a: "A) Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
        b: "B) AWS CloudTrail",
        c: "C) AWS Trusted Advisor",
        d: "D) Amazon Route 53",
        correct: "a",
    },
    {
        question: "Where can a user find information about prohibited actions on the AWS infrastructure?",
        a: "A) AWS Trusted Advisor",
        b: "B) AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        c: "C) AWS Billing Console",
        d: "D) AWS Acceptable Use Policy",
        correct: "d",
    },
];